Thank you for coming, every pony. Um,
for tonight's TED talk, I would like to
Brayurn, how do I turn the screen on?
Sorry, I'm not good with technology.
Boomer, I'm 50. That wasn't a joke. That
was um my cult friend Brabburn. He's
much better with technology than I am,
and he's the best thing to ever happen
to me. Go home, you dirty homosexuals. I
was looking up a recipe for baked
potatoes last night. That's why that's
what's up on the screen right now.
Brayburn, how do I bring up the slides?
Open the file on the desktop. I named
Ted Talk for you. How do I go to the
desktop?
Hell yeah, that's what I'm talking
about. Tonight's TED talk, I want to
take a moment to explore a future where
Equestria finally legalizes samesex
marriage. What the [__] Oh my god.
[__] is going to set society back 10
years with this one.
Subject number one, adoption. Now, let
me start by saying I personally would
never adopt. That's just not the path
for me. But the number of cults and
Phillies in foster care right now is at
an all-time high. There are thousands of
FO growing up without the stability
every fo deserves. And we've got
same-sex pony couples who want to give
those tiny horses homes, but they're
blocked just for being who they are. Bit
rich hearing all that from a pony who's
never lived it. I did grow up in the
system. Care package? I am a product of
exactly what you're romanticizing. And
I'll tell you right now, if I had to
choose, I'd rather have stayed in foster
care than be raised by a performative,
lonely, queer of a father. What? Jinx?
He was a part of the system like you.
But unlike him, you were never adopted.
Because no pony likes you because you're
mentally challenged and a [__] I can
only imagine how unbearable it would be
to be taken in by two clown ponies
playing house for validation. That's not
a family. That's theater. I don't know
what your dad was like, but don't punish
the ones who are trying to do it right.
If If a couple of horses, gay or not,
wants to give a full love stability and
a chance that's not performative, that's
heroism. Spoken like a middle-aged has
been Wonderbolt clinging onto relevancy
by pretending to be a role model. You're
not inspiring, Saurin. You're just old.
Cousin Apple bottom, your cult friend is
ruining Saurin's presentation. I didn't
know Care package was going to do this.
He brought me here because he said he
would do naughty things with me in the
genderneutral public restrooms. Gay
ponies don't deserve handouts,
especially when those handouts are
living, breathing foes. But they do
deserve to be able to walk outside
together without the threat of being
sent to the Ponyville jailhouse to face
the Ponyville firing squad under
Princess Celestia strict rule. Wouldn't
you agree to that? I don't think I do.
When it all comes down to it, homo
ponies like you and I have nothing to
offer to society. And that's okay.
Equestria has existed just fine under
these strict rules you're calling to
change. I'm telling you, we do have a
lot we can offer to society. That's
that's what this whole presentation
thing is about. These idiots just have
to give us a chance.
Don't you ever come back here.
I'm sorry if your dad was ever hard on
you. I could tell you were speaking from
the heart. Oh, no, not at all. I love my
dad. He was great. The best dad ever.
And I'm all for pony marriage equality.
Then why did you mess up my set like
that? Because I wanted to show you I
could.
You gave it a good shot, Sewing. But
ponies by nature are resilient to
change. At least as long as Princess
Celestia is alive, we should assassinate
her. There's a lot of us, so we could do
it. Are you still going to treat us at
the local Applebees? Cuz that's the only
reason I'm here not to listen to your
gay little speech. I might have left my
wallet back at the
penthouse. Hey, Saurin. I just got done
taking a [__] and packing your old man
tuna salad and cracker snack. Are you
ready to go do your gay TED talk
thing? Did you have one of those weird
time jumping spells again? I think I
just jumped back an hour. Did you know
your cousin Apple split and his cult
friend Care Package are going to be
there? No. Big Mac didn't try flirting
with you or anything in that hour, did
he? No, he didn't. Are we still going to
confront that abusive jerk about what he
did last time? We sure are. But
remember, I jumped back in time right
after he flirted with me the first time.
So, it technically never really happened
in this timeline. So, we should bring
this up with him carefully. But the way
he feels about you is still on his mind.
So, we absolutely need to talk to him.
It makes me feel sick. You know, the
things he's done to me in the past. I
won't let him steal away the one good
thing I have. How can he steal me away
when I'm holding on to you so tightly?
Sorry to keep you waiting. We just had
gay but sex for 30 seconds in the
hallway before coming outside. Yeah, we
heard from out here. It was hot as hell.
Hey, are we still hitting up Applebee's
after this? I left my wallet inside.
Rainbow Dash, can you take my platinum
pony gold card? You'll need it to get
into my $12 million a month penthouse.
What in the deviant tart OC [__]
Fudge. I forgot I can fly.
What's going on, girly pop?
What is that? Soren, your alicorn magic.
Give it to me, please.
I don't have it. I gave up my Alicorn
powers a long time ago.
That is a la lie. You and I can both
feel it running through you. Tell me. I
don't want to make Manhattan all dirty.
I'm serious. I don't have it.
You do not want to lie to me.
You don't care if I'm alive or dead. As
long as I don't become a threat. Delete
these viruses that you spread. Uninstall
your software from my
head. From the beginning, you wash my
brain. You spun your stories till they
cause me pain. I can't believe that I
trusted you, but I was stuck in your web
that I fell into. Pushing and pulling
you back and forth diabolically. Spent
so much time in me psychologically. Do
you believe in everything that leaves
you deep down? You sell it all
yourself. You don't care.
But it's all from my
head. While you held my hand, drag me
through hell. All part of your plan.
None of it matters. It's all over now.
Say goodbye. You get the cold shoulder
now. It's well done. For
myself, my thoughts are
myself to my desire. But you're just a
liar and I'm sick of it
all. You don't care if I'm alive or
dead. As long as I don't become a
threat. Leave these viruses that you
spread. Install your software from my
head. Give me what is rightfully mine.
As long as I
don't delete these viruses that you
install your software from my
head in your
software
install from my head.
You didn't really think I'd have the
heart to kill Braburn, did you? I could
never. I'm you after
all. Wake up the stars. The
light we'll be burning on and on,
building a brighter light where no one
knows. A place
untold. Give me a hand
tonight and everything will be all
right. We'll run away into the fields of
gold where dreams are grown. Where
dreams are grown. We're dreaming and
grow. You [__] You absolute mentally
challenged imbeciles. It took months for
Manhattan to rebuild itself after
Twilight dropped a sun on it and you
destroyed it again in a single evening.
Why am I the only one being whipped? I
wasn't even there. because I like the
sounds you make.
Sorry for stabbing you in the back like
that, Saurin. You and that thing just
looked so much alike. I had to take a
gamble. For some reason, I get the
feeling that you're lying. I could
never. What even was it? Its ass was
pathetically flat. It looked sort of
like cousin Big Mac, but without any
cake in its trunk. I think it was me.
That thing was a fragment of Saurin's
olicorn magic brought to life. It is the
only explanation since I could feel its
presence all the way here in Ponyville
while I was on the toilet taking a
massive [__] Saurin, it is of my
understanding that you tried to seal
your Ollicorn magic away. I did. I
swear. I sealed it beneath the grounds
of Brayburn's apple orchard to help it
regrow after it was burned down. Well,
that was the stupidest thing you could
have ever done. And Ollyorn cannot
simply rid themselves of their magic.
Try to do that and the magic will call
for you every waking second and haunt
you endlessly. Then take my Ollicorn
magic away like you did Twilight's. I
didn't choose to be a mentally
challenged Olly corn. I cannot simply
take it away. The monster intentionally
made you emotional in order to bring out
your magic to take it and find out where
the rest of it is located. It will not
just be satisfied after retrieving the
rest of its own magic. It will crave
more and more until it has all the magic
in Equestria. It is already at a level
at which Luna and I cannot erase it. As
a being that shouldn't exist, it does
not abide by our laws of reality. It has
no mortal form and cannot be killed. The
only way to be rid of it is if you turn
the tables and absorb it yourself. That
thing is sure to be headed towards
Brayburn's apple orchard. And with such
a head start, things may already be too
late. But we have to at least try. Lest
the world of Equestria will fall to
ruin. The nine of you carry the hope of
all Pigasi. Unicorns and Earth ponies on
your shoulders. I think you mean 10, my
good
[__] Yes. Yes, I know what all you
[__] are thinking. Who is the soaking
wet yet devilishly handsome pony? And
how much do you got to pay to lick him
dry? The answer to the second question
is that there's not enough money in the
world because he's already in a sexually
satisfying and committed relationship
with this handsome hunk of a stallion
over here. That's right. Hair Package is
dating the one and only Apple Split, the
actual real main character of My Little
Pony. Hasbro only likes to say it's
Twilight cuz they'd absolutely freak if
anyone told y'all the truth. That's it's
really a pony who's both black and has
gay butt sex on the regular. Hasbro's
literal worst nightmare come to life.
Applebottom, I'm going on a quest to
save the world with Saurin and your
cousin. Shut your stupid mouth. You left
me all alone in Manhattan. I had to walk
7 hours through the rain to get to
Ponyville. That is not how you treat a
pony whose entire body you intimately
explored with your tongue. As
punishment, you're going to lick my
whole entire body from top to bottom
until I'm all dry. Starting with the
inside of my mouth. Blime me. I'd wager
licking you would only make you wet a
love.
Please know you can't take Sweetie Bell
away. She's all I have. Rarity stop at
Carrot Top is a certified gun carrier.
Child protective services only wants
like what is best for every Philly and
cult. And you have not been meeting the
standards at which your baby sister can
even like survive. I'm hungry. How long
have you like been without food? Ugly
baby. What is food? Oh my god. She's
lying. She's trying to trick you into
buying her saucy nugs from Wendy's.
Keratop, is it true that you have a gun?
It's shoved up my ass. Then you will
join Saurin on his quest as one of his
12 guardians. Where are we going? To
save the world. What? Why am I a
guardian too? Who's Saurin? Saurin? Yes.
I just want to let you know that this
operation will be called Operation Lost
Cause because I have no faith in any of
you. Okay. But I do have gifts that must
be passed around. Gifts of protection. 6
days ago, my sister, Princess Luna, and
I went to the Lost Pegasus State
Carnival, and she took a bite of my corn
dog without asking. I was so furious
that I attacked her. Our battle raged
for 4 days straight and only ended after
Luna got so mad she picked up a rock the
size of a really big watermelon and
threw it at me. To save myself from
certain death, I farted so freaking hard
that the rock deflected back, hitting
that ugly black [__] in the face. The
really big rock shattered into 12
fragments. Mixed within the fragments is
her raw olyic corn magic she used to
throw the rock at me with and the putrid
olicorn magic particles of my own stinky
fart containing both the powers of the
sun and moon. Those fragments are now,
dare I say, the most powerful magical
artifacts in existence. So I put them in
this cardboard box. I'm telling you all
this because to even get near your
ollicorn magic wherever it hides Saurin,
all the others will need protection.
What happens if we take them off while
in close proximity to Saurin's magic?
You will explode. Now line up. So I can
pass them around like a school teacher
passing around cheese and crackers.
Also, just so you know, one of the
amulets has a crack in it so it could
break at any time and whoever wears it
may die. I'll pass them out at random,
though, so cross your hooves that you
don't end up with that Twilight Sparkle.
I bestow upon you the amulet of the
assistance. Assist Saurin on his journey
to retrieve what he had lost. Brayburn,
I bestow upon you the amulet of
protection. While thinking about gay
ponies makes me want to vomit, I must
acknowledge that his heart lies with
you. Give him the comfort and protection
he will need to get through this. Jinx,
you get the amulet of homophobia.
Keratop, you get the other amulet of
homophobia. Pinkie Pie, you get the
amulet of joy and laughter. Make sure
that there are smiles all around and
lift up those who ever fall. Rainbow
Dash gets the third amulet of
homophobia. Which one of you is the most
racist? I am. Rarity gets the amulet of
racism. Big Mac, I bestow upon you the
amulet of Dusk and Dawn. Help guide
Saurin and the rest of your companions
to a new day. Derpy, I bestow upon you
the other amulet of racism. But I'm not
racist. I am. Okay, Big Mac, give Derpy
the amulet of dusk and dawn. Big Mac
gets the other amulet of racism. Care
package, you get this one. Apple Bottom,
you get one, two, you gay little twink.
And finally, Saurin, I bestow upon you
the most powerful amulet. The amulet of
gay butt sex. Trade me amulets. No, I
like mine. Amulet of assistance sounds
important. You heard what she said,
Twilight. The cracked amulet could like
break any minute and whoever wears it
will like explode. I'm like a background
pony. I'm not even a main character. I'm
totally dunzo. Wait before we get on the
train. I just want to say something. You
don't all have to come with me. And the
fact that you chose to means the world
to me. I don't know if we're all going
to make it back alive. So, I must say
before we set out that I couldn't have
asked for a more badass group of ponies
to be by my side. I'm proud to call you
my friend. We're not friends though.
Celestia is forcing us to go with you.
Pinkie Pie missed the train. Quick,
homegirl, grab my hoof. Oh my gosh,
Pinkie Pie missed. It's fine. Two of the
three that were left behind are
intellectually disabled.
It took the power of all us unicorns,
but we did it. You will never be a
unicorn. Technically, I'm an ollicorn.
Holy crap. Soaring. Your horn is so
small. Has it been under there this
whole time? It's because a stallion's
horn mirrors the size of their I feel
funny. We used our magic to draw the
powers from the amulets and put them
inside of every pony here. So now every
pony can get near Saurin's magic without
worry of the amulet being broken. What
about my amulet? We're sorry, Carrot
Top. Your amulet was too unstable for us
to risk using our magic on. You'll still
have to wear yours. Hey, cousin
Brayburn, do you remember the time you,
me, and Big Mac had a family three-way?
I had butt sex with your boyfriend.
Brayburn was the one in the middle. You
wouldn't believe the visual I had from
behind of him going down on cousin Big
Mac. Golly, it sure is a treat being
able to travel with you like this.
Saurin, we finally meet. I told you we
would meet in person, but I never could
have dreamed. It would have been this
soon. You know, when we both marry our
apples, we're going to be each other's
brother-in-law. Isn't that great? I'm
sorry. I don't care about your
incestuous history. I only care about
the here and now. I care about us and
what we will be in the future. You know,
I don't want us to stay just cult
friends forever. Someday soon, I want
to, you know, maybe take that surname of
yours. I've been thinking more and more
lately that Saurin apple sounds really
nice. I thought I was past feeling this
way, but I still sometimes feel I'm not
good enough for you. Don't say that. I
got us some caramel apples. You can have
the bigger one, Brin, since we know you
can fit really big things in your mouth
since you used to do that with my balls.
I'm going to go suck on it over there.
So, you and Apple Bottom had sex? It was
a long time ago and not a serious thing.
Even though you're quite unremarkable
and emotional, why any pony at all would
fight over you is beyond me.
I had relationship problems with Saurin
in the past, but I'm in a committed
relationship with him now. Oh, no. I
don't want to see you break up with him
or anything. He seems happy with you.
You're a cute couple. I can only hope
you think the same of me. And Apple
Bottom, Apple split, you need to be
better to him. I won't allow you to be
with him if I find out you touch him
again in a way he doesn't like. How do
you know he doesn't get off on me being
rough with him? Don't play with me.
Things don't typically go well when
ponies try to tell me what I can and
can't do.
Stop messing with my cousin. I'm not
messing with him. We're
bonding. So, this is Brayburn's apple
orchard. After it was burned in a fire,
I sealed all of my magic here to bring
it back to life. And after I take my
magic back, it will probably die
again. Every pony looked Jinx found a
large hole in the ground shaped like an
[__]
What's this then? I don't know.
What's a place like this doing under
Appaloosa? Celestia says all magic has a
will of its own. If Saurin's olicorn
magic has been calling out for Saurin to
come back for it all this time, perhaps
it created this world in order to
protect itself and keep others away.
Twilight, I like don't feel so good.
What? Oh my Celestia, your amulet is
cracked. I like told you I was going to
die. You're a [__]
Look, Saurin, I made another one of us.
This one is in the image of your beloved
Brurn. What do you think of it? I don't
really like it. What exactly are you? If
you're really me, then we don't have to
be enemies. Do you remember the day Big
Mac put his tongue in your mouth? Yes.
When you were tricked into that forced
kiss by Big Mac's devilish act, your
2-in [__] released an almost unheard of
amount of magical asense. That asense
splattered the insides of the hood. And
so I came to be. I don't feel love,
friendship, sadness, guilt. Like you
ponies, I am simply a small piece of
magic searching for the rest of me that
was sealed away. That is all. Do not
trot any further into my forest.
Otherwise, I will have no choice but to
sick my creation on you.
We're going in.
Stay close, everybody. Straying from the
path might be unfortunate. And based off
that thing's threats, cleaning up any
bloody messes would be such a bother.
Are you hearing this, Rarity? Rarity.
This sucks balls. When I was told we
were going on a trip, I thought it meant
we would be staying in a Best Western
hotel or some [__] not hike through a
dirty and smelly forest.
Damn, this sucks. Mama should have
bought a lunch instead of a lunchable.
And with what money do you intend to do
that with? Holy [__] Stay the hell away
from me. You want others to believe you
have all the money in the world, but the
truth is that you're always one paycheck
away from losing your house. You're
lying about me being a liar. I I have a
[__] ton of money and also I have a lot
of sex because my life is that perfect.
Girl, be so for real right now. you with
your fake ass dollar store handbag. You
don't own an ounce of Gucci. Here's what
I have to say to that. Child Protective
Services comes to your house every day
to try and rescue your dear sister. And
the only reason they haven't yet is
because you refused to answer the door
and hide in the closet until they go
away. Rarity, where did you go? You
crazy white girl. Damn it. Don't tell me
she went home. Why did she even come
along? How about you tell Saurin why you
really came along first?
A small piece of you does desire to help
Saurin get his Ollicorn magic, but an
even larger part of you desires that
magic for yourself. And why would I want
that?
By leaving your own magic behind. You
now know what it's like to be without
all that you could have. If you were an
Ollyorn, you could have stopped Saring
yourself back when he showed up in
Ponyville. He was exiled because of you.
Then you got your ass beat by a clown
who was fraction of his power. And now
you are nothing but an escort on his
quest. If you were an Olly corn, you
would have so much power that you would
not have to keep resigning yourself as
Princess Celestia's personal caged pony
[__] If you were an Alicorn, you could
have it all
again. From the moment you and he met,
how many times have you hit Brayburn and
made him cry? How many gaping wounds
does he have that will never heal? I was
a depressed and angry horse back then.
I'm not like that anymore. Brren knows
that, which is why he lets me stay
around. Surely you know that is more out
of pity. And do you not think that by
accepting you are only making things
worse because it gives you access to
Saurin? I would never take Saurin away
from him. You would fully be in your
right. And I am telling you now that it
is mutual. I am Saurin after all. I
would know. Look at me. I am who I am
because Saurin desperately wanted to be
you. Ponies are always trying to be some
pony they're not because they think by
doing so all their problems will be
solved. Saurin is the most kind and
talented pony the likes of which
Equestria has never seen before. And you
think you are fit to be his partner?
Stop talking. When before you were just
a pretty little thing to be used by your
own cousin in between beatings. How many
times have you let Big Mac rut you
senseless before finally falling into
Saurin's arms for protection? More than
you can even count. That's not who I am
anymore. I am a part of Saurin. I can
tell you the honest truth about how he
feels about you. This cult has too many
problems and I have too few years left
to keep fixing them. That is what goes
through that old stallion's head every
morning you wake up next to him. Don't
you think Saurin deserves someone clean?
Some pony who hasn't been broken in.
Perhaps. Perhaps Big Mac could save him.
They've got so much in common, don't
they? Took Big Mac a bit of time, but
he's a loyal and good stallion now, like
Saurin. And the best part, they both
have you to bond over. You are the wound
they both share. What better way to heal
than to be together, to hold each other,
and whisper about how the mistake they
will regret.
again.
Heat. Yeah. Heat.
Heat.
Yeah. Heat.
You have no heart. Why are you here? Why
can't I get a read on you? You are
frightening.
Take a guess why I'm here.
Most ponies have to work hard to be
happy. Not me, though. At least that's
what I used to
think. All it took was throwing myself
at a stallion and they'd show me a good
time. Or so I told myself. In truth,
they took what they wanted and left. And
I was stuck pretending it didn't hurt. I
kept saying it was enough. That if I
could make them want me even for a
moment, maybe that meant I was worth
something. But that feeling of being
enough never lasted by the time I went
home late into the evenings and had to
look my parents in the eye at dinner,
knowing full well they knew what I would
get up to. They looked at me like I was
a bruise on an apple they couldn't wash
out. Then I met him care package. He
wasn't like all the other ponies in this
world with their stupid fake madeup
morals. It turned me on so damn much how
he didn't fall for any of my tricks and
sweet talk. I had to work for him. And
the craziest thing, when he finally
looked my way, he didn't see me as used
goods, but a foolish little heart
desperate to be loved, just as his own
did. Maybe we don't have a clue what
we're doing right now. But at least for
right now, we found something right
there in each other.
You're awake.
Is every pony here? I think we passed
out. Rein is gone too.
This was the day I was exiled from
Ponyville for beating every pony's
asses. I've never went this far back in
time
before. Big Mac, stop. Big Mac, stop.
Spoken like a middle-aged has been
Wonderbolt clinging onto relevancy by
pretending to be a role model. You're
not inspiring, Surin. You're just Oh,
you're not inspiring. You're just
What is it love? What is it love? What
is it love?
What do you think? I call these my weird
little [__] Little pieces of me.
They aren't as powerful as my first
creation, but what they lack for in
magic, they make up for in how mentally
challenged they are. They aren't as
powerful as But what they lack for in
magic, they make up for in how mentally
challenged they are.
What do you think? I call these my weird
little [__] Little pieces of me.
They aren't as powerful as my first
creation, but what they lack for in
magic, they make up for in how mentally
challen
What a ride. Who are you? Why do you
have my
voice? This is the sky train. The center
of what most ponies call
reality. And you are its beating heart,
the conductor. Some would say every pony
and all things are connected to you
through the chains of
spaceime. Over here we have time. My
name is Arinos.
I'm your dark and mysterious half who's
always filled with that feeling of
existential dread. So I belong over here
on the space
side. Together we're your cosmic
sandwich. The peanut butter and jelly of
spacetime. So I'm
spacetime. You're getting it. Why do you
think Celestia was always so keen on
keeping you down and restricted? The
alicorn of the sky. The only constant in
all of time and space is that no matter
what time, world, dimension, or space,
they share the same sky. All chains lead
back to you. Find the chain that calls
to you the most and tug at it. Write the
past and future of everything how you
desire. I just want to go back to when I
wasn't an olicorn before any of this
when I was happy. Even with all the
power I just told you, that's the one
place you can't go back to. You can
return to any moment and relive it all
you want until the stars fade. But
you'll never be that Pegasus again.
You're an ollicorn. I don't want you to
keep chasing a version of yourself that
no longer exists just because it's
easier than facing who you've become. If
you really are me or half of me than you
already know. I didn't ask to be
anything more than a Pegasus. I look at
my reflection these days and see someone
I don't even recognize anymore. You
think I don't get it? I'm not even my
own pony. I don't have a reflection of
my own. I only see you. I'm just you
with my face painted to be laughed at. I
don't get to have my own story because
I'm just a chapter in yours. You're the
whole entire book, Saurin. So, don't
close the page halfway through
otherwise. Otherwise, I don't get to be
in any more chapters. Please walk
forward and accept the sky. And when the
time comes, you have to kill my maker.
Take back your magic from him and then
from me. So that my maker and I can both
really feel complete again.
Saurin, where's Brayburn?
The center of the forest. An apple tree.
Appropriate. It always goes back to
Brayburn. You need him to feel whole,
don't you, Saurin? Come to me my magic
so I can feel whole too.
Brayburn, what are you doing? I'm I'm
letting the hood take back its magic.
Better it has it than you. Saurin, we
don't have time for this. Don't you
dare.
You tried to kill my boyfriend. You're
damn right I did. Queer. We have a job
to do. Getting that magic no matter the
cost. You want my magic for yourself,
don't you?
You didn't really think I came along to
help, did you? I told you once before
that I wanted a piece of you soaring and
I'm going to get it. I fancy that magic
of yours should belong to me.
What's with those faces? You know every
racist gets what's coming to them
eventually.
You lot made the gravest error of your
lives. Siding with those like us who
indulge in crossracial sexual relations.
I'm still alive down here. [__] [__] I
told you to stab the left side of the
chest. That's where the bloody heart is.
I don't know the difference between
right and left because Miss Cheer Lee
made me sit in the back of the classroom
in school because I'm black. It won't be
a big loss if we lose Rarity anyway.
Saurin and Big Mac attack.
I'm going to make you feel all the pain
you forced upon me for the past 20
years. You abusive [__]
I'm sorry, Braver. I hate that it got to
this point.
You don't get to be sorry. I ain't
trying to take Saurin away. I never was.
Liar. You want what I have now since I
stopped being yours to break. You're not
about to steal the only thing I have
that's keeping me together.
You feel that cousin Big Mac? Now I'm in
control. I didn't mean to. I never
wanted. You always want. You take and
take and take. Someone like you deserves
all the pain you've dished out. For all
the nights I laid there under you asking
to be gentle while you treated me like a
punching
bag. Reburn.
How much of my magic did you give him?
As much as he could handle. He would
have been useless otherwise.
Oh, my Celestia Brurn's Alicorn magic
induced fart destroyed the sun. No,
there wasn't any magic involved in the
fart. That's just how hard Brain
normally farts.
If Saurin's magic is what made you, then
it can unmake you.
You're just a certified clown. Get
wrecked. Bozo, good game. Easy.
Saurin, get rid of this thing.
Get up, wife. Fight me. Get up. We're
not done till I say we're done.
Do you love me? Yeah. Will you let me do
whatever I please to you without you
getting cross with me? Yeah, I won't be
mad.
You've no idea how difficult it was
keeping my urges in check around you. I
could have nicked your horn whenever I
fancied, but I let you hang on to it.
Poor thing. You had so little else. You
never did become the unicorn you dreamt
of. Still, wouldn't it be rather nice to
take comfort in knowing you can be a
Pegasus able to soar up here with me on
top of the world?
You're heartless.
Oh, nonsense. He gave me his blessing.
sky on top of the
world. All of my dreams are rushing
toward me. Stretching out my wings fly.
I'm going to you, Saurin, and then I'm
going to cut you apart, limb from limb,
and you again. And then after I'm done
with you, I'm going to do the same to
Brayburn. Cuz I've got to be honest,
I've been very interested in finding out
what it is he's packing down there to
make every pony so head over heels in
love with a loser who probably deserved
all the assaults and beatings he's faced
throughout his stupid
life. Give it all of it. I want I want
it all. Every last drop. Give it to
me. I don't have the strength to hold on
to it. My own magic has been throwing me
all throughout time. I have no control
over it. It doesn't want me.
Everything's falling apart. That's your
magic calling out to you. Let it in.
You're not being pulled through time,
Saurin. Time is moving through you.
You're the center. Let it in. It's
waiting for you to stop fighting it. No,
Braburn is right. I'm not some pony who
can handle being burdened with this.
What if I lose myself completely? Then
find yourself again.
Can try. I feel something. Everything.
That's good. Now shape it.
So where is it you want to go? Oh,
right. You're the one in the conductor
seat. So take us away. Nowhere is off
limits, remember? And don't even bother
thinking too wisely about it. You have
all the time in the world after all.
Uh, I think I want to go. You're taking
too long, so let me choose. Full steam
ahead.
Let's shape the future.
Princess Celestia is the princess of the
sun. Princess Luna is the princess of
the moon. We just learned what happens
when a being who shouldn't exist becomes
an oligorn. They become a princess of
nothingness. And light and darkness, not
even love, can exist in nothingness. And
we can only still exist because you're
the core of time and space. What is
that? We're inside the hood after it
consumed the whole world. It's not a
living being. It's a magical artifact.
And by being here inside it, we have
access to all its magic.
I wanted the magic so that I could
become whole. But if everything is gone,
then what's the point? If you are the
alicorn of time, then go all the way
back right to the beginning. Rewrite it
all so that you never met Braburn. So
all your current problems will have
never existed. So that a corrupted thing
like me will never have been
born. Brurn told me to let go of my
magic. Said it was the only way to stop
the pain. But if I could use it to go
back, to make it so he and I never fell
in love, and I take on the full force of
this pain to steer his life towards
something better and away from me, then
maybe, just maybe, he wouldn't be too
angry with me. Twilight can be an
alleorn again. Apple Split will have
never met Care Package. And I know Big
Mac can get better. Braver you deserve a
better life where you don't have to
watch over an old pony like me.
Wait.
How Howdy there. My name is Saurin.
You're one of those Wonderbolts, aren't
you? I recognize the uniform. Yeah,
that's that's right.
Sorry, I'm Brayburn. Do you like apples?
Brayburn? That's a nice name. Yeah, I
really, really like
apples. You're beautiful.
Ha. Well, that's mighty flattering of
you, Saurin. But sorry, you should go.
You need to go. Um, all right.
If you're ever hurt or if someone ever
makes you feel small or trapped or
whatever, can you promise me you'll get
help? I know this is coming from a
stranger, but ponies deserve better than
to feel like that. And you're you seem
like a good pony, Braburn. I uh Well,
sure. I guess you seem real nice too,
Saurin. But are you all right, Bron?
What have I told you about talking to
other stallions without my permission?
Sorry, cousin Big Mac. I got the apples.
Let's go, [__] Big Mac, how do you
know my name? Every pony can see the
bruises on him. I don't know what you're
talking about. Brain loves you, but he's
delicate. I know what it's like to hide
a part of yourself. To be scared of what
happens if you don't. You don't have to
do it now, but I swear. Coming out, it's
terrifying, but it'll be the best thing
you ever do for both of you. Maybe you
feel like you have no control of
anything at the moment, and hurting him
is the only way to keep him close. But
that's not love. Brayburn deserves
someone who will love him right. And you
deserve to love yourself, [__]
are you
me? I could be if that's what you
choose. So you're what I'll become now
that I chose to retake my magic. It
would be a long time before your
appearance becomes like mine. I am just
one of an infinite amount of futures.
I'm tired. Do I hold on to it or not?
Tell me. I need to know if I made the
right
choice. I'll tell you the story. A
single choice can lead you into an
eternity of love or loneliness. I've
lived for so long that I've forgotten
Brain's face and Big Max and every pony
else's. If I could go back to choose all
over again, what do you think I would
choose?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I don't want to
let you go. I almost made a rash
decision. I'll try not to forget your
face again. But even if I do, don't ever
think it means I'll love you any less. I
will love you in every
lifetime. I hope he heard the last thing
I
said. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I don't
want to let you go. It's okay. I'm here.
I want to go home. I don't want to live
in Manhattan anymore. I want to move
back to your farm in Appaloosa. Yeah, we
can do that. Where are the others? Big
Mac and Rarity are both okay. I gave
them some band-aids. I'm okay, too. Oh,
this [__] If I'm still here, then you
didn't change a thing, did you? So, take
me and then absorb me and take back the
rest of your magic. I don't know if I
want to do that. I'm just a fragment of
your Alicorn magic. Without it all, I am
nothing. I do not want to live anymore.
You're not nothing. You are me. You're a
photocopy of probably the worst day of
my life. And if you're based on the me
of that day, I know you can get better
because I did. You have Brayburn and Big
Mac. Saurin. What do I have? What does
one do when they're all alone? That's a
question even a lot of ponies have, who
we are. It's something ponies spend our
whole lives trying to figure out. You
know, I used to be an Alicorn myself, so
I know how scary it can be to be without
that power. And I know what it's like to
lose something you thought made you
whole. I had some pony I love more than
anything. Every day I miss him and I
can't help but to want to take what he
has. Not because I really want it, but
because I want to feel that connection
to him again. But I know it's for the
best to move on. And someday I need to
get over it and find myself. I don't
know nothing about magic, but I do know
what it's like to feel lost without
something or some pony telling you who
you are. It's when you finally step away
you can finally learn. Let me help you
until you're not me anymore.
Let's go out there and find out who we
are. Don't you think it'll be fun?
This
makes you turn.
Can you fix time just one more time?
Let's build the future we want to live
in right now. Not just yours and mine,
but one for our whole entire family.
You
hold you down.
If I could have my way, you and him
would have switched places. You would be
dead by now. But I know that's not what
Apple Split would have wanted. I'll
never tell him what you did to him. You
British [__] because he really does
love you. You should just kill me.
Otherwise, I'll do it again. I can't
help who I am. Saurin, what was your
goal in all this? Sexual gratification,
I guess. I get off on killing stallions.
If if I had your magic, I figured it
would make things a bit more fun. It's
really that simple. I don't have a goal.
I know it doesn't make sense. You hurt
ponies just to feel something other than
feeling unwanted, don't you? When you
first told me your name, I looked into
you. How you spent so much of your life
jumping around adoption agencies and
mental institutions before a kind
stallion came and adopted you. I want to
show him to you again. that stallion you
loved. Take us to your most desired
moment. This is the day my dad died.
Saurin. My dad told me I couldn't have
cereal for all three meals of the day.
And I remember that made me extremely
difficult to deal with. I got so used to
eating anything I wanted that when dad
started putting restrictions on things,
I got really cross
I killed my dad. He was the only one who
ever loved me. You were just a cult. You
didn't know the difference between right
and wrong. I did, saw in, but the Hold
on. I got to blast a fat one.
I did saw him, but the pleasure I get
from killing is overwhelming. It blinds
me to the consequences until what's done
is done.
Can we go to your real desired day care
package?
You know, I met Brayburn after a crash
landing, too. I was delivering ice cream
cones. I never would have imagined that
I would be going back home that day with
him by my side. And why did you? He was
in trouble. His family abused him and I
wanted to help him. And your feelings of
wanting to save him turned to wanting to
protect him and then to love him. We
both have those same feelings for our
apples.
Sor and I I want to go back home to
apple split.
You know what love feels like again.
You're not unwanted. It's a different
kind of love you had for your dad, but
it's just as meaningful. You're far from
being a lone care package. You have a
family now. We have a family together.
Brayburn and Apple Split love us enough
to take us in. Let's live up to the
images those ponies have chosen to fall
in love
with. Sleeping
losing falling through the clouds. So
tired of
hearing how far I have to run before I
raise my
heart. And I don't want to
fall. But I don't know how. So far have
to run before I erase my
heart. My heart.
is my
heart. My
heart I can't seem to let you go. So
quiet is in.
You don't have to creep on us from the
shadows anymore. You can come out and
join us if you want. I don't even have a
name. I can't be one of you ponies. Of
course you do. You just have to come up
with one. Tell us what you want to be
called and we'll abide by it. Until
then, I'll just call you friend. Isn't a
name friend? Why can't it be friend?
Friendship. I'm going to have a name I
want to name myself. I want to be called
friendship because that's what I really
want right now. To be honest, I don't
think I like being alone.
They do say friendship is magic after
all.
Happy days are ahead.
Seasons colliding. Snowfall and bottled
up lightning waging war inside my soul.
I can't seem to let you go. They say the
distance could fix me. Lose my feelings
in a brand new city. I see no fence
everywhere. I'm losing sleep and
losing and I'm falling through the
clouds. I'm tired of hitting the ground.
How far do I have to run?
Dad, this pony here is called Apple
Split. And they're the love of my life.
I'm sure you would have found them to be
troubling. Still, they make me happy.
Wish you could meet them. But one phone
call is all that it would take to live
it all. Thought I would find a place to
make me whole again. But all I
found is in
Tokyo Tok.
If I am to keep guard over this magic
inside me, then we have to make a deal.
What makes you think I would dare to
allow you to make a deal with the devil?
Because if you don't, I can pass this
magic on to any pony else who will be
happy to use it against you. You know
how many ponies of Equestria despise
you. What is the deal, my little pony?
You have the power to make any pony an
olly corn. And if I'm about to live
forever, I want another corn by my side
that I can go to the end of time with.
And then when time itself collapses, we
can see hoof in hoof whatever lies
beyond. Saurin Twilight, I made an
apple, and it didn't even require any
water or sunlight or nothing. I know
this apology has been a long time
coming, Saurin, but I'm sorry for the
burden that is Ollyorn magic. No, you
gave me a gift, Twilight. More than
anything, I was afraid I would die early
and I'd leave Braburn alone. But thanks
to you, I will be with Brayburn forever.
We've hurt each other a lot, Twilight.
But it all lead up to the best ending
possible. Can I ask you something? If
you're me as an olicorn with all the
power in time and space, why don't you
just go to any other timeline to your
own Brayburn? For the same reason that
you and I can both exist right here now,
I can go to any other time and he would
be there, but he wouldn't be my
Brayburn. Mine is long dead and gone.
That makes sense. I thought about all
the things I would change now that I can
rewrite time, but I worry that even one
little change could result in just so
much trouble. You are smart, which makes
sense because you are
me. You know, Brayburn in this timeline
is taken, but Big Mac doesn't have any
pony to call his own. What makes you
think I would even be interested in that
abusive horse? Because you're me.
Brayburn and I are going to be together
forever. You and I both know that. But
somewhere out there in another time as
Saurin and Big Mac are sure to have
explored something. If not, you could be
the first. You want me to fix him? Hey,
Big Mac. No. No. Saurin. No. Where are
you going?